Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art financial records, 1872-1988 COR0004.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Art rental and gift shop, 1949-1980; Series 12
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Shop Reports, 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1974; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Shop Policy and Reports, 1974; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1975; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Shop Reports, 1975-1976; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1976; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1977; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Shop Inventory, 1977; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1978; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1979; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Shop Reports, 1979; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Shop Reports, 1980; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 105)
- Grants and grant proposals, 1967-1979; Series 13
  The series is arranged chronologically by grant application.
  Researchers must also investigate the Development and Membership Records (RG 3) for a complete overview of the Archives grant materials.
  Contains applications for grants, budgets for grant projects, correspondence, memoranda, grant proposals, and status, financial, and summary reports on grants. Granting agencies to which the Corcoran applied include the American Revolutionary Bicentennial Commission, D.C. Dept. of Corrections, D.C. Fine Arts Commission, Mellon Fund, NEA, NEH, Stern Fund, and USIA. The Gallery applied to these agencies and others for aid with specific exhibitions, annual exhibition schedules in general, and special projects, such as the Lorton Prison Art Project. Persons who figure prominently include Gwendolyn Goffe, Francis Harper, Walter Hopps, Vincent Melzac, Jillian Poole, and Roy Siade.
  - Miscellaneous, 1967; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Museum Purchase Plan (NEA), 1969; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Exhibition - The Literary Experience: 200 Years of Genre NEA A70-0-314, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Strong Foundation, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Museum Purchase Plan (NEA), 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Special Education Project Proposals, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Special Education Project Proposals, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Special Education Project Proposals, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Mellon Fund, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - NEA - Artist Fellowship Program NEA A71-0-327, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - NEA - Exhibition Schedule - Matching Grant A71-0-317, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Exhibition Schedule NEA A71-0-317 Continued, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Exhibitions - Matching Grant Continued, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Exhibitions - Matching Grant Continued - 1972-1974 Reports, 1971; Series 13 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - NEA - Renovation - Climate Control NEA A40-20-2418, 1971; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NEA - Exhibition Wilderness NEA A72-0-250, 1971 October 9-November 14; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - NEA - Museum Survey, 1971; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Outreach Program/Demonstration Teams (NEA), 1971; Series 13 (Box 20, Folders 4-6)
  - Outreach Program/Demonstration Teams (NEH) Final Report, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Stern Fund, 1971; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Strong Foundation, 1971; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cafritz Foundation, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Dept. of Corrections - Lorton Prison Program, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - NEA - American Visionary Art A72-0-620, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - NEA - Universal LTD Art Editions - Tanya Grosman A72-0-1180, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - NEA - Utilization of Museum Collections A15797 72, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Pastorale Fund, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Strong Foundation, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Wyeth Endowment, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Dept. of Corrections - Lorton Prison Program, 1973; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - NEA - Aid to Special Exhibitions - Area Show, 1973; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - NEA Museum Purchase Plan, 1973; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - NEA Photography: Cameron, Gossage, Power, 1973; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Special Education Projects, 1973; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Mellon Fund, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - NEA - General Programs Grant, 1974-1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - NEA - Museum Purchase Plan A40-20-344, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - NEA - Ed Muybridge Exhibition, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - NEA - Permanent Collection, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - NEA - Renovation - Climate Control, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - NEA - Anne Truitt Exhibition A40-20-29, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - NEA - Visiting Artists/Specialists Program, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - NEA - Bessie Potter Vonnoh Exhibition, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - USIA - Area Show (19th), 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - NEA - Jacob Frymire Exhibition R50-20-27, 1975; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - NEA - Photography Lecture Series R50-41-14c, 1975; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission - Addison Scurlock Exhibition, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - NEA - Andre, Le VA, and Long Exhibition R70-20-16, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - NEA - Artist in Residence Program RQ0-41-4c, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - NEA - Celebration of Our Country Exhibition, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - NEA - W.W. Corcoran, Patron of the Arts Exhibition, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - NEA - Five Plus One Exhibition R60-20-24B, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - USIA Liberation: 14 American Artists A 17933-24-G, 1976; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Cafritz Foundation - 35th Biennial Exhibition, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - HEW - Corcoran School Library, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - NEA - Artist in Residence Program R70-41-412C, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Gabriel Kohn Exhibition R70-20-15, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - NEA - Morris Louis Exhibition, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - NEA - Tony Smith Exhibition, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - NEA - In Space Exhibition, 1977; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous (Fiscal Year 1977-1978), Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - NEA - Challenge Grant to Corcoran (1978-1981), Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - NEA - Challenge Grant Continued, 1978; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - NEA - Challenge Grant Continued, 1978; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - NEA - Challenge Grant Continued, 1978; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - NEA - Clark Catalog and Exhibition R70-20-66, 1978; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - NEA - Solar Conservation System - Renovation, 1978; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 13 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Miscellaneous subjects, 1934-1989; Series 14
  Arranged alphabetically until the appointment of Gwendolyn Goffe as Director of Finance & Planning in May 1979. The Goffe miscellaneous subject files are arranged chronologically and, thereafter, alphabetically.
  Consists of subject files. The pre-1979 materials include the miscellaneous finance files created during the comptrollerships of G. Herndon Phillips, Frank D. Parulski, Russell Leone, John Albarado, Charles Grunewald, and Robert Stiegler. Subjects of significance include the Corcoran's affiliation with the law firm of Hamilton & Hamilton - annual fees & cases worked on 1971-78; various office machine contracts & service agreements; the American Red Cross rental of Gallery space in the 1950s; and the renovation of the Gift Shop/Salesroom in 1969/70. Also included are statistical reports on Accounts Receivable & Payable (monthly reports); condition of the funds (monthly reports); salaries (annual lists); stock contributions & purchases; trial balances for annual budgets; and purchases of works of art information and statistics.
  Important subjects in the Goffee files include a cost study of evening hours at the Gallery; Sotheby's sale of Corcoran art; Goffe's first report to the Trustees as Director of Finance; and files on various Gallery events such as the Beaux Arts Ball (1979/80, 1980/81), the Surprize Party (1980/81), and Video Artcade (1982/83).
  Attendance reports for 1978-80 and Development/Membership reports for 1978-80 were removed from these miscellaneous finance records and relocated in the Special Events Records and the Development/Membership Records respectively.
  - Accounting - Dept. Codes, 1959-1975; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Accounting - Procedures, 1971; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1963-1964; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1965; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1966; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1967; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1968; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1969; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1971; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable - Mo. Reports, 1973-1974; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - American Assoc. of Museums - Performance Survey, 1977; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Art School - BEOG, NOSL Loans, 1976-1977; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Art School - Sculpture Class and Lab, 1962-1963; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Art School - Store Operation, 1949-1962; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Art Shool - Studio Space Rental, 1951-1953; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Art School - Summer School Budgets, 1951-1964; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Art School - Misc., 1964-1965; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Artist Fellowship Program, 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Attendance Summaries (Annual), 1946-1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Avis Co. - Truck Rental, 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Chapin (Alous) - Apartment Rental, 1968; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Chapman (Joseph) - Fees for Consulting, 1971; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Children's Art Center at CGA - Proposal, 1955; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Christenberry (William) - Fellowship to Brown Univ., 1972; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Collective Bargaining - Survey, 1974; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Columbia School, 1968; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Columbia School, 1969; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Columbia School, 1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Columbia School, 1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Commerce Dept. - Census of Services, 1977; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Common Endowment Fund, 1971; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1962-1963; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1964; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1965; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1966; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1967; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1968; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1969; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Condition of the Funds Mo. Reports, 1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Contributions - Misc. Acknowledgement Corres., 1964-1973; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Contributions - Annual Statistics, 1947-1967; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Contributions - Annual Statistics, 1970-1976; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - D.C. Charitable Solicitation Act, 1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - D.C. Government Surplus Purchases, 1970; Series 14 (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Dues and Subscriptions (Magazines, etc.), 1964-1971; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dupont Center, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dupont Center, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Dupont Center, 1971-1974; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1966-1974; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Etching Press Purchase, 1966; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fire Detection in Gallery, 1971-1976; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gen'l Services Administration - Steam for Gallery, 1952-1978; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Glover, Charles C. Jr. - Contributions, 1962-1965; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Hamilton and Hamilton (Gallery Attnys) Misc. Invoices, Lists of Work Done, 1971-1978; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Inaugural Ball, 1973; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Inaugural Ball, 1973; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts (D.C.), 1951; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - International Art Registry, 1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Joan of Arc Tapestries - Postcards, 1970-1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Kolb Electric Co. - Controversy Over Bill, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Marriott Corp. - Vending Agreement, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Membership Assoc. Fund, 1947-1959; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Multitone Guided Tours (Signal Inc.), 1962-1965; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - National Competition for Playground Sculpture, 1966; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Adm. - Reports, 1972-1979; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Office Machines - Misc. Inventories, Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Office Machines - Misc. Service Agreements, Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Payroll Procedures, 1949-1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. - Financial Consultants, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Piano Purchase, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Printing, Miscellaneous, Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Procurement Procedures, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Red Cross - Rental of Gallery Space, 1952-1954; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Reproduction RIghts and Royalties, Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Salaries, 1952-1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Salaries, 1970-1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Salaries, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Salaries, 1976-1978; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Salesroom Renovation 1-5, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Salesroom Renovation 6-7, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Salesroom Renovation 8-9, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Salesroom Renovation 10-11, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Salesroom Renovation 12, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Salesroom Renovation 1-5, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Salesroom Renovation 6-7, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Salesroom Renovation 7-12, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Salesroom Renovation, 1971; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Service Bureau Company (Payrollers), 1976-1979; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1934-1938; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1939-1940; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1941; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1942-1943; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1944-1945; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1946-1947; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1948-1954; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1955-1965; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1966-1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1970-1971; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1973; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Stock Contributions and Purchases, 1974-1978; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Summer in the Parks - Art and Youth Program, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Telephone Installation, 1968; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Trial Balance, 1963-1964; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Trial Balance, 1965-1966; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Trial Balance, 1967-1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Trial Balance, 1970-1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Trial Balance, 1973-1975; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Insurance Survey, 1976; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Eugen Weisz Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1954-1962; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Wiles (Robert) - Conservation and Restoration, 1971-1975; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Women's Committee (Budgets, etc.), 1959-1963; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Women's Committee (Budgets, etc.), 1963-1966; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Women's Committee (Budgets, etc.), 1966-1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Women's Committee (Budgets, etc.), 1970-1978; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Works of Art Purchases, 1947-1967; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Works of Art Purchases, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Works of Art Purchases, 1970; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Works of Art Purchases, 1971-1976; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Works of Art Purchases, 1977-1979; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Frank Parulski, 1967; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Frank Parulski, 1968; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Frank Parulski, 1969; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Russell Leone 1-5, 1971; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Russell Leone 6-12, 1971; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - John Albarado, 1972; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - John Albarado, 1973; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Chas. Grunewald - Endowment Investment Income, 1973-1975; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Chas. Grunewald 1-5, 1974; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Chas. Grunewald 6-12, 1974; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Chas. Grunewald, 1975; Series 14 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Comptroller's Misc. Files - Robert Steigler, 1975-1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Goffe Subject Files - American Univ. Intern Agreement, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Gwen Goffe Subj. File - "Architecture is Elementary" Budget, 1978-1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Auditorium Renovation, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Beaux Arts Ball, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Goffe Subject Ales - Builoing Project Fund, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Copyright, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Evening Hours: Cost Study, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Handicapped: Access to Gallery, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Goffe Subject Files - HEW: Sex Discrimination, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Loans of Works of Art Policy, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Occup. Safety and Health Adm., 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Report to Trustees, 1979 May 21; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Salaries, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Sotheby's Sale, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Super Dinner (School of Art), 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Misc. Correspondence, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Beaux Arts Ball, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Goffe Subject Files - C and P Telephone Proposal, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Endowment Fund Descriptions, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Goffe Subject Files - "Images of the 70's" Exhibition, 1980 January 18-March 10; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Goffe Subject Files - School Tuition Increase, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Surprize Party, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Fiscal Year Change, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Goffe Subject Files - Video Artcade, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Job Descriptions, 1949; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Job Descriptions, 1950-1975; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Job Descriptions, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Garnishments, 1960-1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Officer Francis Harper: Misc. Corres., 1977-1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Administrative office F. Harper - Misc. Corres., 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Development Officer: Winter, 1977; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Development Secretary: Fall, 1977; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Director of Public Relations: Fall, 1977; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Discrimination Case: Anthony Brown vs CGA: Fall, 1977; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Education Director Fall, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Executive Secretary (To Chief Exec. Officer): Spring, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Secretary to Curator of Collections: Winter, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Secretary to Director: Fall, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Security Officer: Winter, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Shop Administator/Manager: Winter, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Shop Assistant: Winter, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Weekend Information Desk Help: Spring, 1978; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Administrative Officer: Winter, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Archivist: Winter, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folders 45-48)
  - Curator of Washington Art: Spring, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Development Research Assistant: Fall, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Education Officer: Summer, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Information Desk: Education Fall, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Shop Assistant: Spring, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Staff Accountant, 1979; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Assistant to Archivist: Summer, 1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Assistant to Director of Development: Spring, 1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Assistant Registrar: Fall, 1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Dean of the School: Advertisement Copy, Job Description (Fall), 1980; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 58)